A Guide to the Papers of Clifford Dowdey
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Clifford Dowdey 1967-1972
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
3809-m
This collection consists of 14 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was gifted to the library in 1973 January.
Contents List
- Francis Berkeley to Clifford Dowdey 1967 Feb 7, ALS
  3 pp.
- J. Clemens to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Aug 7, TLS
  1 p.
- Melvin B. Yoken to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Sep 17, ALS
  2 pp.
- John Cushman to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Oct 23, TLS
- Lucy Daniels (Mrs. Jonathan Daniels) to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Oct 8, TLS
- Colgate Darden to Clifford Dowdey 1967 Feb 13, LTS
- Maurice Duke to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Nov 5, TLS
- Linwood Holton to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Oct 18, TLS
- Jay Howland to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Oct 16, TL
- Sarah Lockwood to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Jun 4, TLS
- Charles McDowell to Clifford Dowdey Wednesday, TLS
- Edgar F. Shannon to Clifford Dowdey 1967 Feb 13, TLS
- Peter Shepherd to Clifford Dowdey 1972 July 13, TLS
- Sir John Wheeler-Bennett to Clifford Dowdey 1972 Jan 24, ALS